[Music]
My name is Felix. I work as an actual
analyst in the GB valuation team at Manu
[Music]
Life. The favorite part of my job in the
GB valuation team is I got a lot of
opportunities to interpret the story
behind different numbers. The actual
developer program also allow us to
rotate between different teams every few
years. And even when I was a co-op, I
was often encouraged to um really expand
on my current skill set to take on
larger projects to think big. The amount
of trust and support that I received
from different teammates really made my
experience at Marife unique. It's also
nice to know that when I'm in marri
life, the actual development program
provides great exam support to help us
get our
destination. Everyone I've met here is
so welcoming and supportive that I never
felt disconnected with the community.
And I can see that my life really builds
a diverse and thriving working
environment.
[Music]